Khameye (David) Khamhuang

Nashville, TN 37011 | Phone: 615-987-4598 | Email: khameye19888@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/khameye-david-khamhuang-36735117b | Github: https://github.com/dkahuna | Portfolio: https://dkahuna.github.io/Live_Portfolio/

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer graduate while working full time 40+ hours per week. Coming from hands-on warehouse floor production to making problem solving software. The warehouse field instilled me with tremendous amounts of leadership skills while also collaborating with a variety of many teams at a fast, communicative, and successive pace. Using those experiences to translate to other situations continues to help personal growth in new challenges that come across.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, Python, MySQL, Node.Js, React.js, Git, GitHub, APIs, MongoDB, Express, jQuery, Firebase, Handlebars, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Media Queries, Heroku, Command- Line, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word

Projects

Waste-to-Go | Front-End Developer | Deployed Link: N/A Code: https://github.com/edwardsjtimothy/Project_1

Provide a brief overview of the project you worked on here.

- **Role**: Collaborated the UI/UX. Creating the GPS functionality/feature
- Utilized: HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, marker icons and navigation from Google Maps API

Employee Hour Tracker | Full Stack Developer | Deployed Link:

https://project-2000.herokuapp.com/

Code: https://github.com/simonk16/project2

Provide a brief overview of the project you worked on here.

- **Role**: Lead and mold the team into the direction of completion. ORM(Object-Relational Mapping)
- Utilized: HTML5, CSS3, Node.js, MySQL, Express, Passport, d3.js, Handlebars

Liri-Node-App | Back-End Developer | Deployed Link: N/A

Code: https://github.com/dkahuna/liri-node-app

Provide a brief overview of the project you worked on here.

- Role: Responsible for single-handedly Designing and Developing the website
- **Utilized**: Node.js, MySQL

EXPERIENCE

Hennessy Ind.; La Vergne, TN **Shipping/Receiving Lead**

03/2011-11/2019

Trained and lead a team of 25+ people without loss of productivity or man hours on multiple tire changer assembly lines. Implemented new and innovative procedures, systems and equipment to improve current production processes and support engineers. Acted as Department Lead in multiple departments due to experience, work ethic and aptitude to learn skills outside of primary duties.

- Re-routed an oil line that was causing malfunction to main production units. Reducing 'wear-n-tear' and warranty claims.
- Lead & met daily target(s) or higher during 4th quarter of the year with insufficient/untrained staff.
- Trained most employees within residing department(s).

Chonburi Muay Thai; Nashville, TN **Coach/Instructor**

01/2014 - Present

Leading groups or one-on-one with self-defense, discipline, motivating ways to incorporate the mindsets obtained through rigorous and prosperous training with he/she day to day tasks.

- Obtained/defended Light-Heavyweight title of TN while working full-time(40+ hrs) and attending school part-time
- Competes at National level.
- Travels to train and corner competitors with Head Coach.

EDUCATION

Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN Full Stack Web Development | Coding Certificate | 2019

A 24-week intensive boot camp program focused on gaining technical programming and market-driven skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, Database Theory, MongoDB, MySQL.